var myQuestions = [
    {
      question: "William Shakespeare mainly wrote which kind of poem?",
      answers: {
        a: 'Limerick',
        b: 'Epic',
        c: 'Sonnet'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "How many plays did Shakespeare write?",
        answers: {
          a: '29',
          b: '39',
          c: '49'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the longest play of Shakespeare, with over 4,000 lines??",
        answers: {
          a: 'Hamlet',
          b: 'Macbeth',
          c: 'Romeo and Juliet'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "How old was Shakespeare when he died?",
        answers: {
          a: '42',
          b: '52',
          c: '62'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "In Shakespeare’s plays, how many times does a character commit suicide?",
        answers: {
          a: '5',
          b: '8',
          c: '13'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "The tragedy Hamlet is set in the Kronborg Castle in which country?",
        answers: {
          a: 'Denmark',
          b: 'Germany',
          c: 'Sweden'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Which kind of play is Romeo and Juliet?",
        answers: {
          a: 'Tragedy',
          b: 'History',
          c: 'Monologue'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the age of Juliet in Romeo and Juliet?",
        answers: {
          a: '13',
          b: '16',
          c: '19'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },
    {
        question: " The play Romeo and Juliet is set in which Italian city?",
        answers: {
          a: 'Florence',
          b: 'Napoli',
          c: 'Verona'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: "The words “to be or not to be” is made by which fictional character in a Shakespeare’s play?",
      answers: {
        a: 'Hamlet',
        b: 'Macbeth',
        c: 'Juliet Capulet'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'a'
    }
]